Silver Eyes
Bear’s Baumkuchen Shop
The Angel and The Protector}
That’s some good cake.
What a pathetic form…
…Iorogi.
Ah! It’s Kobato-chan!
Good morning, Kobato-chan!
Good morning!
Kobato-chan, can I tie a ribbon on the puppy?
Puppy?
Do you mean Ioryogi-san?
Come on! Gimme a break here!
Yes! Please do!
He’s cute!
Yes! Ioryogi-san likes it!
Who the hell would like this?!
Good morning!
Good morning, Kobato-chan.
I hope we’ll have a good day today.
Yes!
Well, I’m off, Ioryogi-san.
Why does she carry that thing around with her?
I’m sure it’s precious to her.
Time to cook, time to cook…
…tasty and delicious baumkuchen.
Cook them, cook them.
That’s right, bake and cook them!
The bear in the woods will be baking… them.
Annoying.
Hurry up and get in here, Ginsei!
He’s not here, you know.
I know.
Then what did you come here for?
I just want to know something.
What is he thinking?
Why ask me that?
Fine then.
The reason we look the way we do is
because of the dweller of the spirit world.
Why suddenly bring-
So how did it all begin?
The Celestial World.
The Human World.
The Nether World.
And then the Spirit World.
The only ones not aware of those separate
worlds are the humans living in their world.
The Celestial World has
angels under God’s command.
The Nether World contains
demons under Satan’s command.
We of the Spirit World are under
the command of the Spirit Master.
Those separate worlds
share a non-aggression pact.
But that idiot Ioryogi…
All right, that somewhat idiotic Ioryogi.
All this happened because he waged a war against the Celestial World.
The reason Ioryogi started a
war with the Celestial World…
…was because there was
something there he wanted dearly.
However…
He failed to obtain it.
Yeah.
He could have done what the son of
Satan would have done and stolen it.
We ended up losing,
and he was made into a stuffed animal as
penance for breaking the non-aggression pact.
I’m now a bear working in a baumkuchen shop.
And Zuishou is now some strange little bird.
Even God has only so much patience.
We were all willing participants, but the
ringleader got the brunt of the punishment.
So how can Iorogi return to the Spirit World?
Until that child’s wish is granted, Ioryogi will remain in that form…
…unable to return to the Spirit World.
Wish?
She must heal the grieving
hearts belonging to the humans.
When she fills up that bottle, her wish will be granted.
It was God’s will for him to assist her.
I don’t know what’s going on in his head.
But I’ll tell you this much: after
he arrived in the Human World…
No, after he ended up
with that child, he changed.
So let’s just leave him alone for a while.
And you can have this-
Geez!
And it tastes good too.
I hope none of my old comrades see me like this!
Oh?
Come tag me, I’m right here!
Kobato-chan, good morning!
Doumoto-san!
Why are you at the preschool?
I have a little business with Kiyokazu.
Everyone, time for lunch!
Wash your hands and go inside!
Okay!
Kiyokazu!
What are you doing here?
I think you should come to the
seminar today, so I came to invite you.
I’m not going.
But it’s the class you wanted!
Excuse me, what’s a “seminar”?
A seminar class. At college.
Ah, so it’s for college learning!
Right.
You were absent the last time,
so you should really come today.
Please go, Fujimoto-san!
Can’t do it. Busy.
Fujimoto-san!
Kobato-chan…
It’s all right. I have an idea.
You’ve done enough for today. You have an important seminar this afternoon.
Sayaka-san…
I've also come here to help several times.
So I knew just what to do.
The kids will be taking afternoon naps soon, and I have Kobato-chan here to help. We’ll be fine.
But…
Fujimoto-kun.
You’re always a real lifesaver.
But I still want you to attend your college.
Please.
Yes.
He’s obeying her.
He only listens to what Sayaka-sensei says.
Dress me up as some
fairy-tale character, will they!
See you, Kobato-chan. I’ll come again.
Yes! Please come again!
See you later!
Take care!
I’ll do my best to fill in for Fujimoto-san!
Oh, that’s amazing!
Dammit! That Fujimoto punk
made the knot too tight to get off!
I can’t thank you enough for today.
Your coming here really helped us out.
O-Oh, you’re welcome!
Get some rest once you return home.
Yes!
That ribbon looks good on Ioryogi-chan.
Ioryogi… chan?
Yes!
I’ll see you tomorrow!
It’s still pretty hot out.
A leafy place might be cooler.
This feels better. Right, Ioryogi-san?
That hurts! What do you think you’re doing?!
You were all scrunched up right here.
Know why?
Are you perhaps hungry?
Kobato.
The seasons are passing us by.
You didn’t come here just
to help out at a preschool.
But I had to work hard filling in for
Fujimoto-san when he wasn’t there today.
That’s what I’m talking about.
You have to do what you’re supposed to be doing!
If you don’t fill this bottle up
quickly, your wish won’t be granted.
Ginsei?
Is that a friend of yours, Ioryogi-san?
Ioryogi-san!
So that’s her?
Kobato!
Ioryogi-san…
Huh? What’s that?
Bastard. If you break that, I’ll make you regret it.
Why?
Why do you remain in the
Human World in that form?
Because it’s something I have to do.
Genko-sama!
Zuishou! Don’t flap your wings in here!
You’ll get your feathers in the batter!
I hear what you’re saying, but I’m still a bird.
I know, I know. So, what’s up?
Oh, that’s right!
I think that slavedriving selfish
guy who’s now a stuffed animal,
and that other guy that had a violent past are about to enter a critical situation!
Oh, is that right?
Huh? That’s it?
Here, take this with you.
Give it to the loser as a get-well gift.
Are you sure we should leave them alone?
Their fight will be of epic proportions!
Neither of us could stop them even if we tried.
Ioryogi originally took that guy under his wing.
He even gave him his name.
Since his eye is silver in color,
he was called Ginsei - Quicksilver.
No matter the circumstances, that’s how it’ll be with them.
Or so I thought. But then
they began exchanging blows.
And how.
He took him in and gave him his name.
So now he maintains his obsession with Ioryogi.
They are the only ones who can settle their feud.
Give back that bottle!
Why not take it yourself?
“Ioryogi-san.”
Keep it up if you wanna get fried!
You’re not going to pin anyone down while in that form.
You son of a…
Simply pathetic. Your appearance. Your name.
Who is “Ioryogi” anyway?
“Io… ryo?”
“Iorogi!”
“Io… ryogi.”
It’s “Iorogi!”
“I… o… ryogi?”
No! It’s “Ioryogi!”
Huh?
Yes! Ioryogi-san!
I grew to like the name she calls me.
Now hand back the bottle.
Say you’ll come back to the Spirit World.
I told you I need to be here.
So I’m not going back.
Not until I finish my job.
You’re talking about that wish?
What does that girl mean to you?
That girl…
…has put me through a lot of pain and suffering.
Then we can just eliminate her.
What?
If we remove the girl, there won’t be any wish, and you will have to return to the Spirit World.
That’s what the old you would do.
Got that right.
She’s one clumsy oaf, without a lick of common sense.
I will do my best!
She’s always putting off
what she came here to do.
And she works herself to death for
other people without even being asked.
But still…
I can’t hate how she’s such a hopeless screw-up.
You didn’t answer me.
You’re squeezing out the stuffing, you bastard!
If she doesn’t fill the bottle, her wish won’t come true.
Ginsei!
In that case…
Once we take this away…
Stop!
Right now you’re in no position to give orders!
Ginsei!
I beg you!
Give me back the bottle.
Without it, Kobato will…
I beg you.
…after he ended up with that child, he changed.
You’re begging me?
The old you would never
even dream of doing that.
Hurry and accomplish your goal.
Ginsei…
Ioryogi-san!
Kobato-san?
Kohaku-san!
What’s the matter?
Ioryogi-san has gone missing!
Ioryogi-san is presently in Sakura Park…
Come on, try to catch me!
Why you…!
Since he was playfully scampering after a friend from the Spirit World, I didn’t call out to him.
Sakura Park? Thank you very much!
You’re very welcome!
Crap, this useless body of mine!
Still, having come this far…
That hurts, jackass!
Ioryogi-san!
Ioryogi-san! Where are you?!
Hey!
Fujimoto-san!
Here.
Ioryogi-san!
Thank goodness, Ioryogi-san!
Thank you very much for finding Ioryogi-san!
Sure…
Ioryogi-san got himself lost.
Lost?
I’m really glad that Ioryogi-san is okay!
So, this thing is that important to you?
Yes!
Ioryogi-san and I are always together!
This is good!
That bear sure knows what I go for.
It looks really good on you!
Why you little…!
Ioryogi-san?
Thank you for getting back the bottle for me.
I’m really grateful.
Dobato!
Minus 200 points!
Why did you let your precious bottle get stolen?! You’re slacking off!
I’m sorry.
What is this? Dress-up day?
Wherever I go, people are tying ribbons on me!
Ioryogi-san and I are always together!
Ioryogi-san?
What?
You really do look good with ribbons!
No, I don’t!
Of course you do! Look, if we tie this one on here…
Stop that!
Then if we tie another one on here…
I told you to stop, dammit!
Oh, and let’s tie one more…
Now I can’t even talk!